Finding Aid for the Michael D. Intriligator Papers LSC.2323
UCLA Library Special Collections
Michael D. Intriligator papers
1962-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
Intriligator, Michael D., 1938-2014
LSC.2323
36.6 Linear Feet (89 boxes, 3 shoe boxes, and 1 flat box) and 0.044 GB (2,432 digital files)
Michael D. Intriligator was an American economist. He joined the UCLA faculty in 1963 as an assistant professor of economics, and later held appointments in political science and policy studies. His research interests were mathematical economic theory, strategy and arms control, peace and security, nuclear proliferation, and health care reform. The papers span 1962-2012 and include professional correspondence, in both paper and digital formats; research notes and files; authored articles, conference speeches and presentations; materials related to book publications; as well as lecture notes and course syllabi and related documentation. This collection also includes correspondence, memos, reports, and promotional materials related to Intriligator's work as director of the UCLA Jacob Marschak Interdisciplinary Colloquium, the UCLA Center for International and Strategic Affairs (CISA), the UCLA Burkle Center for International Relations, and a Senior Fellow at the Milken Institute.
Conditions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Source of Acquisition
Devrie Intriligator; Gift; 2015
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9981037823606533
Biography
Michael D. Intriligator was an American economist at UCLA, where he taught in the economics, political studies, and policy studies departments. Born on February 5, 1938 in Freeport, New York, Intriligator received a Bachelor in Science degree in economics from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) in 1959, a Master's degree in economics from Yale University in 1960, and a PhD in economics from MIT in 1963.
Intriligator joined the UCLA faculty in 1963 as an assistant professor of economics, with later joint appointments in political science and policy studies. His research interests were mathematical economic theory, strategy and arms control, peace and security, nuclear proliferation, and health care reform. His 1971 book, Mathematical Optimization and Economic Theory, brought previously inaccessible mathematical techniques into the mainstream field. He also coedited the Handbook of Economics (1980-2004) book series and coauthored Climate Change and the Energy Problem (2012).
Intriligator served as director of the UCLA Jacob Marschak Interdisciplinary Colloquium on Mathematics in the Behavioral Sciences from 1977-1999, and as co-director from 1999-2013. He was also director of the UCLA Center for International and Strategic Affairs (CISA) from 1982-1992 and director of the Burkle Center for International Relations from 2000-2002. Along with this work at UCLA, Intriligator was also a Senior Fellow at the Milken Institute in Santa Monica, a Senior Fellow of the Gorbachev Foundation of North America, a Foreign Member of the Russian Academy of Science, and a member of the Council on Foreign Relations.
He was married to Devrie Intriligator, a space physicist at the Carmel Research Center in Santa Monica. Intriligator passed away on June 23, 2014 in Los Angeles.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of materials related to the professional research and scholarship, as well as teaching career of economist Michael D. Intriligator, a UCLA professor within the Departments of Economics, Political Science, and Public Policy. His research interests were mathematical economic theory, strategy and arms control, peace and security, nuclear proliferation, and health care reform. The papers include professional correspondence, in both paper and digital formats; research notes and files; authored articles, conference speeches and presentations; materials related to book publications; as well as lecture notes and course syllabi and related documentation. This collection also includes correspondence, memos, reports, and promotional materials related to Intriligator's work as director of the UCLA Jacob Marschak Interdisciplinary Colloquium, the UCLA Center for International and Strategic Affairs (CISA), the UCLA Burkle Center for International Relations, and a Senior Fellow at the Milken Institute.
Organization and Arrangement
This collection has been arranged in the following series:
Series 1: Correspondence, 1987-2011
Series 2: Professional scholarship, 1963-2009
Subseries 2.1: Research materials, 1963-2007
Subseries 2.2: Articles, papers, and presentations, 1963-2009
Subseries 2.3: Book publications, 1963-2008
Series 3: Teaching and university affairs, 1962-2012
Subseries 3.1: Administrative and biographical, 1965-2009
Subseries 3.2: Courses, 1962-2008
Subseries 3.3: Marschak Colloquium, 1962-2012
Subseries 3.4: Center for International and Strategic Affairs, 1980-1994
Subseries 3.5: Burkle Center for International Relations, 1998-2009
Subseries 3.6: Milken Institute, 1992-2007
Series 4: Born-digital materials, 1997-2011
United States -- Foreign relations -- Soviet Union.; Arms race.; Nuclear energy -- Government policy.; Economists -- United States -- Archives.; Intriligator, Michael D., 1938-2014 -- Archives; University of California, Los Angeles. Department of Economics--Faculty -- Archives
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1987-2011
  Scope and Content
  This series is composed of professional correspondence between Intriligator and colleagues at UCLA, other universities, as well as national and international organizations and policy institutions. Topics include administrative functions, conference travel planning, research and publication discussions, and articles revisions. Many of the paper materials are printouts of email correspondence--duplications may exist between paper in this series and digital files in Series 4. The series is organized by date.
  - Correspondence., 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence., 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1-7, Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence., 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1-2, Box 3, Folder 1-6)
  - Correspondence., 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence., 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence., 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence., 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7-8, Box 5, Folder 1-6)
  - Correspondence., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 1-2, Box 5, Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence., 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence., 2007 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence., 2008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Series 2: Professional scholarship, 1963-2009
  This series contains materials related to Intriligator's professional scholarship, including research, papers and presentations, articles, and book publications. Intriligator wrote and presented extensively on issues related to nuclear policy, arms races and control, terrorism, globalization, health policy, and US relations with the Soviet Union and Russia. The materials include correspondence, drafts, reviews, event promotional materials, publisher contracts and royalty statements, and other administrative documents. Files within each subseries are organized alphabetically by title or subject.
  - Subseries 2.1: Research materials., 1963-2007
    This subseries contains Intriligator's handwritten notes on various economic theories and mathematical economics concepts, as well as research materials relating to various topics he wrote extensively on including arms races and control, nuclear policy, and the Soviet Union and Russia. Early research on arms races and deterrence, as well as nuclear policy was funded by the RAND Corporation. Other funding agencies include the National Science Foundation (NSF), UC Council on Research, as well as the North American Rockwell and other private funding agencies and donors.
    - Handwritten notes: General economics., circa 1963-1978 (Box 7, Folder 1-4, Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Handwritten notes: A-Z., undated (Box 8, Folder 1-6, Box 9, Folder 1-8, Box 7, Folder 1-2, Box 10, Box 11, Folder 1-5)
    - Academic Border Crossing., circa 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Arms races and arms control., 1963-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7-10, Box 12, Folder 1-5)
      Includes reports and documents published through research carried out in consultation with the RAND Corporation.
    - Civil military strategies., 1965 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Computational Working Group., 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Council on Research., 2000 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Disarmament., 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Econometric model building., 1970, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Globalization., 2004-2005 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - Iraq War., 2004 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Medicare., 1998-2004 (Box 13, Folder 4-5)
    - Middle East and Russia., 2001 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - North American Rockwell Project., 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1, Box 13, Folder 7-9)
    - Nuclear weapons policy., 1975-2004 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
    - Programme for Promoting Nuclear Non-Proliferation., 1989-1998 (Box 14, Folder 5-8)
    - Research and Development Output., 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Russia-Soviet Union., 1992-2007 (Box 15, Folder 1-8)
    - September 11., 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Teaching and research., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Report on study for the United State Air Force and the RAND Corporation that considered some aspects of the allocation of scientific effort between teaching and research.
    - Wealth distribution., 1976 August (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Weapons of mass destruction and terrorism., 2004 (Box 16, Folder 6-7)
  - Subseries 2.2: Articles, papers, and presentations., 1963-2009
    This subseries contains drafts, final versions, presentation slides, correspondence, and promotional materials for articles and papers authored by Intriligator for publication and presentation at conferences and workshops done locally and internationally.
    - Agenda for Action., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - AIDS., 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Alcoholism., 1983 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Allied Social Science Association., 1988 December (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - American Economic Review., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - American German Roundtable., 1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - American Health Lawyers Association., 1999 March (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - American Statistical Association., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Arms control., 1968-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1-3, Box 17, Folder 6-17)
    - Arms races., 1964-2000 (Box 19, Folder 1-11, Box 20, Folder 1-12, Box 18, Folder 4-13)
    - Baker Institute., 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Baltic States., 1997 October (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Bangkok., 1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Behavioral sciences., circa 1990-1992 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Bio-terrorism., 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Brand name prescription drugs antitrust litigation., 1998 May (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Budapest., 2004 June-July (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - California Republic Conference., 2001 February (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Center for Economic Design., 1998, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
    - China-Russia., 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Conferencia Sobre Transicion y Consolidacion Democraticas., 2001 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Conflict theory., 1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Concept of Peace Divided., 2000 May 28 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Cooperative Models in International Relations., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Copenhagen Conference: Accidental Nuclear War., 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Copenhagen Consensus., 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
    - Corporate restructuring., 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Council on Foreign Relations., 1989 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Countering bioterrorism., 2002 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Current Wisdom., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Defence economics., 1978-1992 (Box 23, Folder 4-9)
    - Disarmament., 1967-2006 (Box 23, Folder 10-12, Box 24, Folder 1-3)
    - Drug evaluation., 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - East Asia., 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - East-West Conflict., 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Econometrics., 1972-1992 (Box 25, Folder 1-4, Box 24, Folder 7-9)
    - Economics: General topics., 1963-2004 (Box 27, Folder 1-3, Box 25, Folder 5-11, Box 30, Folder 5-6, Box 26, Folder 1-23)
    - Economists Against the Arms Race., 1985-2004 (Box 28, Folder 1-8, Box 27, Folder 4-9)
    - Energy., 1974-2007 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
    - Enlargement of the European Union., 1999 February (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - European Meeting of the Econometric Society., 1988 August-September (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Eytan Sheshinski project., 1980-1989 (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
    - Financial economic crisis., 2009 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - FISCIT-LINK Teleconference., 1992 June 29 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Fukuoka University., 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1, Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Game theory., 1980 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Gas tax., 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - General theory of planning., 1980-1995 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Georgia., 1998 December (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - German American Roundtable and Rice University visit., 1987 September (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Global Cooperation for a Better World., 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Global security., 1978-2008 (Box 30, Folder 10-12, Box 31, Folder 1-12)
    - Globalization., 1991-2007 (Box 32, Folder 1-5, Box 31, Folder 13-15)
    - Gorbachev Foundation., 1999 March (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Guerilla warfare., 1989, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 7-8)
    - Healthcare., 1991-1998 (Box 32, Folder 9-13, Box 33, Folder 1-12)
    - House of Representatives hearing., 1977 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Heuristic decision rules., undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Identification., 1967 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation., 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
    - Integrative Graduate Education Research and Traineeship (IGERT)., 1998-2004 (Box 34, Folder 1-2, Box 33, Folder 16-17)
    - Interdisciplinary Dimensions and Economic Analysis., 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - International Association of University Presidents., 1990-1992 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - International Defence Economics Defence Association., 1987-1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - International Economic Association., 1983, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
    - International Institute for Strategic Studies., 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - International Monetary Fund., 1997 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - International policy: Cooperation., circa 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - International regimes., circa 1983-1988 (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
    - International Studies Association., 1998 March 18 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Istituto Affari Internazionali., 2002 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Japan., 1985 April 12 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Labor., 1979-1996 (Box 35, Folder 3-5)
    - Marshall Plan., 1988-1999 (Box 35, Folder 6-9)
    - Mathematical social sciences., 1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Medicare., 1993-2004 (Box 35, Folder 11-15, Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Middle East., circa 1989-1996 (Box 36, Folder 2-5)
    - Military industrial complex., circa 1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Milken Institute Review., 1999 November (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Missile defense., 2000 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Moscow conferences., 1991, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 9-10)
    - National Institute of Defense, Japan., 1995 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - New School of Athens., 2008 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Nonlinear programming., 1987 (Box 36, Folder 13-14)
    - Nuclear policy., 1977-2006 (Box 38, Folder 1-5, Box 36, Folder 15-17, Box 37, Folder 1-18)
    - Parnu conference, Estonia., 1992-1998 (Box 38, Folder 6-8)
    - Peace and pacifism., 1990, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
    - Pews meeting, Washington DC., 1990 October 4 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Pharmaceutical economics., 1996 May (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Planning National Defense Technology., 1990 August (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Plato Society., 1997, 2000 (Box 38, Folder 14-15)
    - Policy analysis., 1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Privatization., 1997 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Psychology., 1989 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Public decision making., 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Pugwash Conference., 1983-1989 (Box 39, Folder 4-6)
    - Questia Media., 2000 June (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Russia-Soviet Union., 1987-2000 (Box 42, Folder 1-7, Box 41, Folder 1-11, Box 40, Folder 1-15, Box 39, Folder 8-18)
    - Southern California Consortium on International Studies., 2001 April (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Space Future Forum., 1987 October (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Star Wars missile defense system., circa 1985 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Strasbourg Colloquium., 1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Taipei., 2003 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Terrorism and weapons of mass destruction., 2000-2007 (Box 43, Folder 1, Box 42, Folder 14)
    - "Third World Peace.", 1988 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Toda Institute for Global Peace and Policy Research., 2002 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Trade and aid., 1966 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - United Nations., 1990-2002 (Box 43, Folder 5-10)
    - United States economy., circa 1976-2004 (Box 44, Folder 1-6)
    - United States-Russia-Soviet Union relations., 1983-1992 (Box 45, Folder 1, Box 44, Folder 7-10)
    - United States Soviet Cooperation in Africa., 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 2-4)
    - War., 1985 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Wealth distribution., 1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Western Economic Association., 1988 July (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Western Management Science Institute., 1964 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Why Not Return to a 'Walk in The Woods?', undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Wingspread Conference., 1990 December (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - World Bank., 1991-1999 (Box 45, Folder 11-14)
  - Subseries 2.3: Book publications., 1963-2008
    This subseries contains materials related to book publications that Intriligator authored and/or edited, including the Advanced Textbooks in Economics series (1974-1994), Countering Terrorism and WMD (2006), and the Handbooks in Economics series (1980-2004). The Handbooks in Economics series was co-edited with fellow economist and Noble Prize winner Kenneth Arrow. A large portion of the materials are correspondence with co-editors, publishers, and writers. The subseries also includes section drafts, publisher contracts, royalty statements, publicity, and reviews. Intriligator's PhD dissertation is included in this subseries.
    - Advanced Textbooks in Economics: General and correspondence., 1974-1994 (Box 46, Folder 1-8, Box 45, Folder 15-16)
    - Advanced Textbooks in Economics: Volumes 1-32, circa 1980-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1-6, Box 47, Folder 1-16, Box 46, Folder 9-17)
    - Committee on the Undergraduate Program in Mathematics (CUPM)-Math Social Science Board (MSSB) Project., 1973-1974 (Box 49, Folder 1-3, Box 48, Folder 7-11)
    - Contributions of Conflict Management., 2007-2008 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Countering Terrorism and WMD: Creating a Global Counter-Terrorism Network., 2004 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - DC Heath and Company., 1989 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Econometric Models, Techniques, and Applications., 1975-1995 (Box 50, Folder 1-8, Box 49, Folder 7-8, Box 51, Folder 1-3)
    - Elsevier: Correspondence., 1988-2001 (Box 51, Folder 4-5)
    - Essays on Productivity and Savings, PhD dissertation., 1963 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Frontiers of Quantitative Economics., 1971-1975 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Handbooks in Economics: Numerous volumes., circa 1984-2004 (Box 54, Folder 1-12, Box 53, Folder 1-11, Box 52, Folder 1-9, Box 51, Folder 8, Box 56, Folder 1, Box 55)
    - Handbooks in Economics: Publisher correspondence and royalty statements., 1990-2001 (Box 56, Folder 2-7)
    - Mathematical Concepts in Economics., 1979 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Mathematical Optimization and Economic Theory., 1968-1997 (Box 57, Folder 1-5, Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Principles of Macroeconomic Modeling., 2001 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Problems in Mathematical Economics., circa 1981-1983 (Box 57, Folder 7-9, Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Publisher correspondence, publicity, and royalty statements., 1983-2001 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Spanish translations., 1985-1993 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Series 3: Teaching and university affairs, 1962-2012
  This series includes materials related to Intriligator's occupation as a faculty member predominantly at UCLA, including biographical materials, course materials and syllabi, correspondence with colleagues and students, administrative and planning documents, lectures and presentations delivered, and published work. There are also some materials from courses that Intriligator taught at USC and CalTech, as well as materials from his activities with the Milken Institute in Santa Monica.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  SERIES CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Subseries 3.1: Administrative and biographical., 1965-2009
    This subseries contains materials documenting Intriligator's professional work, including curriculum vitae, business cards, and UCLA departmental materials.
    SUBSERIES CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. All requests to access special collections material must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
    - Biographical materials., 1999-2008 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
    - Biographical materials: Devrie Intriligator., undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Business cards and rolodex., undated (Box 58, Folder 7, Box 59-61, Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - UCLA: Council on Research., 1999-2001 (Box 68, Folder 3-5)
    - UCLA: Economics Department administrative materials., 1986-2009 (Box 63, Folder 1-3, Box 62, Folder 6-7)
    - UCLA: Faculty and professional activities., 1973-1999 (Box 63, Folder 4-7)
    - UCLA: Faculty reviews., 1965-1987 (Box 64, Folder 1-2, Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles-St. Petersburg Sister City Committee., 1999-2000 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - UCLA: Master of International Policy Degree Program., 1998 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - "PA and MA Stuff", circa 1990-1999 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      2 unprocessed SuperDisks (.24 GB)
      The library cannot provide access to the files contained in the SuperDisks due to lack of required hardware. For more information, please contact the reference desk.
    - Photographs: Conferences and events., 1970s-1980s, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3.2: Courses., 1962-2008
    This subseries contains course syllabi, lecture notes, administrative materials, and assignments from manly courses that Intriligator taught at UCLA. There are also materials from courses taught at USC and CalTech from 1971-1974.
    - UCLA: Economics course materials collected from other faculty., 1965-1976 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - UCLA: Economics 11., 1993 (Box 64, Folder 8-9)
    - UCLA: Economics 100., 1962-1974 (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
    - UCLA: Economics 101., 1969-1972 (Box 65, Folder 5-14, Box 66, Folder 1-3)
    - UCLA: Economics 103/Political Science 139., 1977-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1, Box 66, Folder 3-11)
    - UCLA: Economics 135., 1964 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - UCLA: Economics 143/Boston College: Economics 125., 1962-1965 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - UCLA: Economics 144., 1964-1997 (Box 67, Folder 4-10)
    - UCLA: Economics 145., 1966-1975 (Box 68, Folder 1-5, Box 67, Folder 11)
    - UCLA: Economics 147., 1973-1993 (Box 69, Folder 1-9, Box 68, Folder 6-14)